issekhon.117@gmail.com

http://www.sfu.ca/~issekhon/portfolio.html

About Me

I am a game designer and programmer with one year of academic experience working with Unity and C#, and three years with OOP languages. That experience includes designing and programming game systems like player movement, animation, gameplay mechanics, level scripting and GUI. I regularly work in teams with artists and designers, often taking on the role of Director and Programmer.

Software and Languages

- Unity
- C#
- Java
- C++
- C
- Maya
- Git
- Processing/Arduino
- Adobe Illustrator

Education

BSc, Major in Interactive Arts and Technology

Simon Fraser University, Surrey, B.C. Concentration in Interactive Systems 3.33 / 4.33 GPA Planned Graduation Fall 2020 Surrey, B.C.

Game Development Experience

Programmer I Academic Project July 2017 - August 2017

- Designed ZERO, a 2D puzzle platformer game, within a team of 4 that was the most successful project among the 20 teams in a third-year game design course.
- Organized team roles, responsibilities and schedule to ensure deadlines were met.
- Programmed the game in Unity with C# scripts to create a fully functional alpha build.
- Playtested the prototype with target demographic and analyzed feedback to improve the mechanics.

Programmer I Academic Project June 2017 - July 2017

- Redesigned an existing game in a different genre, based on industry standard game design principles, to create a more engaging game called Ant Commander.
- Designed unique enemy and boss mechanics for varied, challenging gameplay and excellent difficulty flow.
- Programmed gameplay in Unity with C# scripts, resulting in a full demo with very few bugs.

Other Experience

Technical Assistant

January 2016 - Present

Sekhon Medical & Dental Clinic, Surrey

 Train staff weekly with learning Electronic Medical Records (EMR) software to improve digital service.

Volunteer Coach

September 2009 - August 2010

One of two coaches for an elementary basketball team.

 Tailored practice routines for kids aged 10 - 12 to keep team organized and ready for upcoming games.